"lang"
{ 
"Language" "English" 
"Tokens" 
{ 
	"testcommands"			"<clr:255,0,0>This is red<I> and italics<B> and<cr>bold<B><I><clr:255,255,255> white again."

	"ddawg.hey01"		"Hey! Over here!"
	"ddawg.cough01"		"*cough*"
	"ddawg.cough02"		"*cough*"
	"ddawg.no01"		"I can't go on much longer, doc. You're better off leaving me here."
	"ddawg.brief01"		"You got the call too, huh? We were headed to the lighthouse when that damn gunship found us."
	"ddawg.brief02"		"It's a clever one, doc: wiped us all out. Hope you have better luck then we had. You're probably better off avoiding it then getting its attention."

	"fb.radio01"		"<I>Hello? Hello? If anyone out there can here me, we need help. The combine's hit us hard and out thumper is down. We're trapped near the old lighthouse. We've got dead, dying, and wounded. PLease, come guickly.<I>"
	"fb.intro01"		"Docter Freeman! I'd never figured they'd send you. I can't belive you're here. I guess you turned on our thumper, huh? You're absolutely amaz--"
	"fb.intro02"		"One second, you!"
	"fb.intro03"		"Better hurry, doc: that gunship's still out there. We've a rocket launcher at the lighthouse, just through that door. It should do the trick for ya."
	"fb.outro01"		"Wow! That was amazin' doc! I mean, I was inside the whole time, but it sounded amazing."
	"fb.outro02"		"You really showed that gunship."
	"fb.outro03"		"Well, uh, we better start packing up. We have a long hike ahead."

} 
}
